She's fast asleep.
That means we get some alone time.
Hang on, Bell...!
Shh. You'll wake the children.
We've got time. Want another one?
No matter how many we have,
my whole life is dedicated to you, Bell.
Oh, Hinata...
G'morning.
Good morning.
Well, afternoon, actually.
That's fine. It's our day off—
Good morning, Bell. This is my—
I'll kill you.
You swore you'd dedicate your life to me,
and yet you have a child
with another woman?!
U-Uh, Bell...?
Wait, when did I say that...?
HINATA, YOU CHEATER!
H-Hold on a minute!
Natsuki?
Mhm. She's my aunt's daughter,
but I'm looking after her
until later this evening.
My mom and dad got called
into work at the last minute,
and I'm not confident on my own.
So, I asked Sunohara for help.
That makes more sense.
Sorry, you guys.
I don't necessarily mind, but...
I don't have experience
taking care of kids, either.
Wh-What is it?
Hey, not my hair—!
I think she's curious about your hair.
Stop that. Be a good girl, okay?
Mama...
I-I guess she must really like Bell...
Come to think of it,
my aunt has long hair like hers.
Jeez... Look, I'm not your mom, so—
What happened?!
Diaper change, maybe?
Where is it...?
That's not it.
Huh?
Tremble
She's hungry, and...
she's anxious, more than anything.
Being separated from her mom.
Here we go.
What are you doing, Bell?!
Huh? Well, I can't do much about
her empty stomach,
but I figured this might calm her down.
Sh-She stopped crying...?
Y'see?
Mama...
Oof, she's sucking hard...
She must be starving.
Sakura, get her food ready
while I keep her occupied.
On it! I'm gonna borrow your kitchen.
That was amazing, Bell.
But how'd you know?
A dark elf's intuition?
Just kidding.
Babies' feelings are pretty straightforward,
so it's easy to get a sense of their mood.
O-Oh...
You can join her, if you like.
My left side is open.
I'll pass!
Aw, what a shame...
Sunohara... you perv.
N-No! That wasn't what I...!
Maybe when I'm older,
mine will be more...
Huh? What'd you just say?
N-Nothing!
H-Here, Nacchan! Food's ready!
Wow, she's drinking it like crazy.
She must've been hungry.
Seems like she wants to play.
This sure is a lot of work...
I know, right?
Oh, Sunohara!
Good afternoon!
Oh my, a baby...
Does she belong to you two?
No, she's not ours!
Would you like to buy something?
No, not today.
Maybe the next time there's a sale.
Wh-What's wrong?
I think she peed.
Seriously?!
Wait here, Sunohara.
Wow, so much!
You're good at this.
My aunt taught me how to do it.
Does she belong to you two?
No, she's not ours!
Can you teach me, too?
How to change a diaper?
Yeah. For future reference.
Huh, somebody's eager.
Like this?
Yup! Slide the nappy a little farther back.
We need a splash guard...
Is something wrong, Bell?
Oh, it's nothing.
Let's head back to the apartment.
That feels nice...
Hey, are you sure you're alright?
I was thinking about how you'd
make a good mom, Sakura.
Huh?
I used to think I wanted kids,
but my confidence went out the window.
Bell...
Hey, it's okay.
What's wrong?
It's time for her nap,
but I can't get her to settle down.
Be a good girl, Nacchan!
Let me do it.
She's finally out.
Bell, that was amazing!
Shh. You'll wake her.
She's fast asleep.
Don't second guess yourself.
Huh?
I think you'll make a great mom, Bell.
Thanks.
Want to hold her?
Nah, I'm good.
I'd feel bad if I woke her up.
Looks like Bell fell asleep, too.
Maybe now would be a good time
to get dinner started.
Oh, I'll give you a hand.
I think I'll make Bell's favorite tonight.
She worked hard looking after
the baby today.
That's sweet of you. And earlier...
they looked like a married couple.
I wonder if that's what Sunohara and I
look like right now...
Mochida? Is something wrong?
Sunohara, how do you feel about Bell?
What?
Is she a friend? Something more?
But you two aren't dating, are you?
No, we're not...
Um, in that case—
Seems like she's hungry.
Do we have any milk?
I-I'll get a bottle ready!
Can I try giving it to her?
Is it yummy, Nacchan?
There, there...
Let's hope you grow up to be
as beautiful as your mama.
Aw, Papa...
I want ten more of them.
Hinata, are you serious...?
Would you do it for me?
Of course!
That's better.
Uh, what's the matter, you two?
Nothing!
Thanks for all your help.
I couldn't have done it without you guys.
No problem at all.
It was good experience.
True.
Still... I had fun.
See ya.
Kids, huh...
Hinata?
Do you want one of your own?
What?
It's all I could think about
while we were on baby duty.
"If I had children with Hinata,
what would they look like?"
Hey—! Knock it off, Bell!
Don't worry.
We learned a lot today.
We can take care of a baby.
That's not the issue!
Oh, you don't believe me?
Then...
Here, go ahead.
B-Bell?!
You seemed awfully curious
when I was feeding the baby.
You do want a taste, don't you?
N-No, that's not—
C'mon, don't be shy.
I know how much you wove my boobs.
Ooh! You use your tongue like a big boy!
Th-This isn't right...!
Leave the parenting to me.
All you have to do, Hinata,
is give me lots and lots of your love.
We'll be one big happy family!
Sh-She's intense...
So long as you're in the mood...
you and I can do it right here and now.
No... It's too soon...
Too soon? That's okay.
Premature or late,
I'll take whatever you have to offer.
That isn't what I meant!
Hi-na-ta...
I-I said stop!
Sorry, Sunohara, I forgot Nacchan's—
Oh god, I'm so sorry!
This isn't what it looks like!